It must be tiring for you.
肯定让你身心俱疲
Well, I admire your strength.
我欣赏你的坚强
I know it must be hard for you to be strong all the time for these girls.
我知道在这些女生面前一直故作坚强一定很辛苦
You know, they're lucky to have a woman such as yourself to keep going for all of them.
能有你这样的女人来维持学校是她们的幸运
They can't know what it's like out there.
她们不可能知道外面的情形
There's no sense to be made of it.
没什么能理解的
Did you have someone before the war?
你在战前有爱人吗
Well, I'm sorry.
对不起
I was a coward to leave,
之前 我像个懦夫一样离开了
but you don't realize what battle really is until you've seen it.
但是只有亲眼看到 你才会知道战场是什么样子
I had nothing.
一无所有
I took 300 dollars to take another man's place.
我收了三千美金 替另一个人当兵